# REY ELLIOT HERNANDEZ GABRIEL

## MS Architecture

**OPT Approved** 

reygabriel.ph@gmail.com +1-323-868-8546

linkedin.com/in/revgabriel

#### **SUMMARY**

Rey is an MS Architecture student from the Philippines, currently based in California, where he is researching opportunities for circular communities in developing regions. He is a registered architect in the Philippines and has a graduate diploma in Marketing.

He is a designer with over seven years of architectural design experience, ranging from residential high-rise and mixed-use architectural design in Asia, sustainability, corporate communications, and architectural journalism. His graduate studies focused on tall buildings, wood construction, public health, and the business of design.

## **CORE COMPETENCIES**

#### Design

Design Thinking, Design Research Concept Development

## **Marketing & Communications**

Brand Management, Identity Systems Copy Writing, Storytelling

#### **Others**

Architectural Writing, Systems Thinking Research, Attention to Detail

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

#### 3D Modelling, CAD, & BIM

SketchUp, AutoCAD, Revit, Rhino

## **Graphics & Layout**

Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Procreate

#### Visualization

Enscape, Lumion, Twinmotion

#### **Other Tools**

Microsoft Excel, Notion

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Master of Science, Architecture

California Polytechnic State University | San Luis Obispo, CA March 2024 | Current GPA: 3.987

#### Graduate Diploma, Marketing

Ateneo Graduate School of Business | Makati, Philippines Batch of 2022

#### Bachelor of Science, Architecture

University of Santo Tomas | Manila, Philippines Batch of 2014

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Winter Intern at Andrew Goodwin Designs

January 2024 - March 2024 | San Luis Obispo, CA

Commercial Marketing

Worked on marketing material updates and new marketing asset layouts that communicate the firm's design and service approach / Produced a user interface assessment of the firm's existing digital platforms / Developed project drawings for the firm's commercial portfolio

#### Architect II - CallisonRTKL at Arcadis

June 2018 - April 2021 | Manila, Philippines

Mixed-Use Tall Buildings Concept to DD Presentations

Developed design proposals for several high-rise residential, commercial, and large mixed-use developments in Asia as part of the Manila Design Team / Produced brand-integrated design narratives and copy for proposals, presentation design, layout, and assets that enable effective communication of the architectural design process to the client / Executed pre-design research work - ranging from front-end context and market research, competitor analysis, to trends analysis

#### Research Assistant - CallisonRTKL at Arcadis

October 2016 - June 2018 | Manila, Philippines

Sustainability Research Presentations Data Analysis

Worked on sustainability research initiatives with the Performance-Driven Design<sup>SM</sup> Team including the assessment and visualization of client sustainability metrics & performance, identifying trends and new research, and documenting data for sustainability compliance

## Junior Architect at AyalaLand Premier

June 2014 - September 2015 | Manila, Philippines

Luxury Residential Leisure Masterplan Design Management

Assisted lead project architect in the masterplanning, design, and design management of high-end leisure and suburban neighborhood developments via plan development and documentation from initial schematic phase to final permit package, data tabulations for permitting and price allocation studies

#### CERTIFICATION

#### Social Change Leadership Certificate

Cal Poly Center of Leadership - 2023

### **Global Shapers Program**

Arcadis - 2017

## Philippine Registered and Licensed Architect

Professional Regulation Commission - 2016